Venue Of The Emmanuel TV Partner Meeting In The UK
The New Morning Water
Emmanuel TV Partners Gather In The UK To Receive The New Morning Water
You're welcome in Jesus' name to the Emmanuel TV partner meeting here in London, UK.
I'm Mark Kenwright, and I'm from Cornwall.
My wife and I are looking forward to receiving the New Morning Water,
meeting with the Emmanuel TV team and receiving from the Holy Spirit.
My name is Elin. I come from Scotland.
So you have travelled all the way down from Scotland to attend this special meeting?
Yes, I have.
Amen! What are your expectations from today's meeting?
Big transformation, and I will see everything become new.
The reason why I came here is because I want to share the New Morning Water
with all my friends in Hong Kong and all over the world.
It's not just for me, it's going to bless everyone.
People should watch Emmanuel TV and believe in God. That everything is possible with Him.
Emmanuel TV is changing lives, changing the world, changing everything.
Amen! It's certainly changing lives, changing the world in Jesus' name.
Emmanuel!
My name is Ruby. I come from Stockholm, Sweden.
So, you mean you flew in straight from Sweden, just for the meeting today?
Exactly. I am just excited to be here and looking forward to what God is going to do today in our lives.
Based on what I have already watched on Emmanuel TV and the experience in South Africa,
I am looking forward to another time of God's goodness and power
flowing through this medium of the New Morning Water,
bringing deliverance, healing and salvation to all that are here.
I believe that people are really expectant to receive their breakthrough before they leave.
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are watching,
I would encourage you to be part of the Emmanuel TV partnership.
It's such a blessing, a great privilege to be part of this ministry.
Thousands and thousands of people are being reached through Emmanuel TV partnership.
It's another way to express your love.
Your giving will go a long way to bless many lives, restore hopeless situations
and give them hope and another chance for them to see life where there seems to be no life.
So, be part of Emmanuel TV partnership and you will be blessed.
Emmanuel! It's a new beginning! Amen!
Thank you very much. My name is Margarita.
I am an Italian living in Dublin. I came from Ireland this morning.
It's a great honour being here at this meeting.
My expectation is very big.
I expect my life to change greatly.
I have a business with my husband - an online business.
I expect prosperity, breakthrough in my life and in the life of my husband.
That's why as soon as I got the invitation, I came. I didn't hesitate at all.
I know this is a great instrument - this New Morning Water.
It's a great instrument of blessing for this 2018.
I am a partner since 2006.
Since then, I saw my life improving.
Now, I have a good job. I graduated and I never lack.
If you don't give, you will never receive.
So, I advise you to be a partner of Emmanuel TV because the reaching out and helping
that the Emmanuel TV family is doing is so mighty and great.
It's a real honour to be part of this project.
Banquet Held During The Emmanuel TV Partner Meeting In The UK
The Emmanuel TV partner meeting in London, UK, where the partners from all over Europe have gathered
together, specially invited by Prophet T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel TV team.
Right now, as they have shared a meal together, we want to hear from some of them.
Can you tell us your name and where you are from?
Yes. My name is Natalia and I'm from Sweden.
I'm originally from Iraq but I live in Sweden.
So you mean you flew in all the way from Sweden to be here with us today?
Yes, absolutely.
Wonderful! Can you tell us your expectations of the meeting today with the Emmanuel TV partners?
Wow! I know it's like a blessing to me and to all of us here.
I'm really so happy to see so many people that came from a lot of different countries.
My mum and I are praying to have such a meeting in Sweden, so I'm really happy.
What can you say about the New Morning Water which Prophet T.B. Joshua sent specifically for the partners?
Wow! I don't know what to say, but we saw some videos on Emmanuel TV and we were so happy.
We were praying that God should send that New Morning Water to us and
He listened to our prayers. So, we are very happy.
It's not about the money or anything because God will pay back so much more.
I mean blessings, good health. So it's not like you give and you don't receive.
God blesses you more and more, the more you give.
And of course, you give with love.
We would like to hear a word from your mother.
Can she tell us her name first?
My name is Mona George, and I'm originally from Iraq but I live in Sweden.
What's your expectation from the Emmanuel TV partner meeting today?
I'm very happy to be here and I'm so happy to see the Emmanuel TV team here in the UK.
We're praying, of course, for you to come to Sweden and visit us.
We saw on Emmanuel TV how the people got delivered just by touching the water.
It's really a blessing from the prophet of God to send that New Morning Water to us.
It's a blessing to our lives.
Thank you.
My name Nelson Gil Gomez. I'm from Portugal living in Manchester.
You've come from Manchester to London today for the meeting?
Yes.
What can you say about being an Emmanuel TV partner? How has it changed your life?
It has changed many things in my life because the first time when I went to Nigeria,
I was separated from my wife.
After that, we reconciled and I am back together with my wife.
So, we are very happy.
I just want to advise everyone to be a partner of Emmanuel TV and The SCOAN
because it's a place where people feel good and where you can see a lot of miracles.
So, I advise them to become Emmanuel TV partners.
My first language is Portuguese, but I try my best in English.
Expectations of the Emmanuel TV
Partner Meeting in the UK
Thank you so much for sharing this with us. God bless you, thank you. Enjoy your meal.
Thank you very much. Thanks.
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
You can see the reaction as people are receiving the New Morning Water.
This is the power of God at work.
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
Who are you in this body? Speak out!
Who are you?
Who are you in this body?
How many of you are in this body?
Speak out!
Who are you?
Who is number one?
Spiritual husband.
Who is number two?
Snake.
Move like a snake.
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
Now stand up.
What is this?
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
What happened?
What's wrong with this?
It's paining my hand.
Take it.
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
Glory be to God! She's been set free through the medium of the New Morning Water
which has been affected by the Holy Spirit.
Let us give thanks to Jesus Christ.
How are you feeling?
I'm feeling okay.
Tell us - what happened to you just now as you touched the New Morning Water?
I saw a bright light coming towards me and it shook my body.
How are you feeling right now?
I am feeling okay.
Glory be to God!
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
See what the Spirit of God is doing as the people are receiving the New Morning Water.
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
Who are you in this body? Who are you?
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
Who are you in this body? How have you destroyed her?
My name is Nombuso Mngomezulu.
I'm from the UK. I live in York but I'm South African.
When I was collecting the New Morning Water, I started shaking.
I felt like there was electricity all over my hand.
I couldn't hold the booklet and the New Morning Water, so I fell and I started rolling on the floor.
I felt like something was shocking me when I was trying to pick up the New Morning Water,
so, I wasn't able to pick it up. I ended up falling.
For me, It's a new beginning and all my problems have come to an end.
I know it's a new beginning this year for me. Thank You, Jesus.
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
My name is Mrs Ogadinma.
I'm originally from Nigeria but I reside in the UK.
This is my husband beside me - my loving husband Fred.
It's a great experience.
It's actually something that I cannot really explain.
The Holy Spirit actually took control of today and
I know our story has changed from this moment in Jesus' name.
Amen! And we saw when you went up to receive your own New Morning Water
sent to you by Prophet T.B. Joshua. We saw the reaction.
You were under the influence of the Holy Spirit. What happened to you?
I can't really explain what happened. I found myself on the floor.
I think the presence of the Holy Spirit took total control of me.
I believe I've been delivered by His special grace in Jesus' name.
Amen.
I feel free, I feel joy inside of me, I feel light, I feel happy.
Thank You, Jesus.
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
The Spirit of God took control just as she merely touched the New Morning Water.
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
Who are you? Speak out!
Who are you?
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
Who are you? Speak out!
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
How did you destroy her?
I killed her husband.
What is this?
Speak out! What is this?
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
What is this? Speak!
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
That is deliverance in the power of the Holy Spirit through the New Morning Water
which has been affected by the Holy Spirit.
Emmanuel TV Partners Receiving
The New Morning Water In The UK
My name is Aderonke Adesanya.
I originally come from Nigeria but I live in Ireland.
I could feel the presence of God from inside out, and immediately we were asked to be on the queue,
I was vibrating from my head to my toes. I just thank God for today.
We saw what happened when you went forward to receive your own New Morning Water.
What actually happened to me was something I knew wasn't right.
I sometimes dream seeing things from my father's house.
But today, the Lord just let me know that it is finished.
I trembled in awe of His faithfulness.
How are you feeling now?
I'm very fine. I'm okay.
I thank God for His faithfulness.
My name is Marco, and I'm from Russia.
Sir, can you tell us - what was your experience at the partner meeting today in the UK?
We are partners from all over the world. I came from Russia.
We were gifted with the New Morning Water sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua to the UK.
God is real and powerful. He loves us, so He immediately delivered people.
Some manifested.
The power of God is here with us at this event.
The revival in Europe has started.
It starts from today in London, UK.
I will use the New Morning Water on my family, friends and all the needy that will come my way.
I believe that God who sent us to apply the New Morning Water will show us His love,
His power to deliver, heal and save people.
And I want to thank Prophet T.B. Joshua for his love and his care for humanity
because he's a man of humanity, not just for Christians.
He's a wonderful gift that God gave to our generation.
I'm Shiromi Ternborg.
I'm originally from Sri Lanka but I came now from Sweden.
And today, you are here for the New Morning Water meeting.
Here in London for the first time, the New Morning Water has come to Europe, sent by Prophet T.B. Joshua.
What was your experience of today?
Love.
I experienced His great love.
I'm so grateful that God knew me even before I was formed in my mother's womb
and that He has called me by my name and has chosen me.
God is going to do mighty things and our past is over.
God has begun a new thing. I'm so grateful because I can be a vessel of God now.
We thank God for your life and we thank you so much for being a partner of Emanuel TV
and joining us in Christ's mission to change lives, nations and the world.
We just want to encourage you that as you continue to be part of Christ's mission,
the best is yet to come in Jesus' name.
Amen! Hallelujah! Thank You, Jesus.
My name is Natalia. I'm originally from Iraq but I'm living in Sweden.
Today, you were here for the New Morning Water meeting. What was your experience of today?
There are no words to describe it.
I'm so happy to be here and to see all the brothers and sisters from all around the world,
and to receive this New Morning Water is like receiving Jesus' presence
because we could feel Jesus' presence all over the place.
I'm very happy.
I saw a lot of people that got delivered and they were vomiting out substances.
Demons could not resist Jesus' presence here, it was really great.
A lot of people got delivered, and for sure, blessed now too.
What message are you going to be taking back home to your people
concerning what you saw and what you heard?
Wow. It's all about love.
Jesus loves us so we have to love one another.
This is something that I have really learned from the Prophet and from the messages that we heard here.
That we should hold no offence, no matter what.
Jesus is love and we should show love and give love and God will bless us for that, in Jesus' name.
Thank You, Jesus.